dedicatedmedia.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Dedicated Media

### What information is collected?

**Personally Identifiable (PII) Consumer Data  
**Dedicated Media does not collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) via our Technology.

**Non-Personally Identifiable (Non-PII) Consumer Data  
**While visiting the web site of one of Dedicated Media’ business customers, including advertisers and web publishers (referred to as “Business Customers”) Dedicated Media may collect anonymous data. This anonymous data contains information such as a web user’s IP address, web pages which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us or a third party advertising technology vendor such as DoubleClick, Inc. Dedicated Media or a third party advertising technology vendor, may use different types of technologies to collect this type of information, including cookies and pixels. None of the foregoing information (collectively referred to as “non-personally identifiable data”), by itself, or together, can by its nature be tracked to a specific individual’s personally identifiable information. Cookies will remain active for no longer than 30 days.

We license and otherwise obtain all types of information from various other companies, including research companies, data aggregation companies and other third party companies. Data sets may include information about you or your demographic segment that such companies have licensed, purchased or collected. We use this information for all the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and for any other purpose that we chose.

**How Is Such Information Used?  
**Dedicated Media will use your non-personal information in order to better target advertisements and to improve our advertising systems and products. Dedicated Media adheres to the NAI’s requirements with respect to sensitive consumer information, and does not target users on the basis of health conditions or interest in health-related subjects.

**Third Party Information Gathering  
**This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Dedicated Media. Dedicated Media will not share any Non-PII data with any third parties, with the exception of DoubleClick and Appnexus, who we use to deliver targeted advertising messages.

**CONSUMER CHOICE  
****  
****Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data – Use of Cookies & Opting-Out  
**Dedicated Media uses both Doubleclick and Appnexus ad-serving technologies to deliver better, targeted marketing messages to individuals. These tools are used for the sole purpose of providing more relevant advertisements to that user. We believe that the use of such tools assists in providing a more meaningful web-surfing experience. If you would like to opt-out from having Dedicated Media collect your Non-PII, please visit the following links:

Upon clicking the link above, your browser automatically downloads an “opt-out cookie” that stops the tracking of non-PII data through Doubleclick.  
Simply check the “opt-out” button and an “opt-out cookie” will be placed on your computer that stops the tracking of non-PII data through AppNexus.

Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you will need to return to the above websites to opt-out again.

**Deleting your PII  
**Dedicated Media makes significant efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use various technologies, including, in certain instances, encryption, to ensure the highest security standards. Any data that is stored on Dedicated Media’ servers is treated as confidential and is not generally available to the public. Dedicated Media has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating our security measures does exist.

**Securtiy Precautions  
**Dedicated Media makes significant efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use various technologies, including, in certain instances, encryption, to ensure the highest security standards. Any data that is stored on Dedicated Media’ servers is treated as confidential and is not generally available to the public. Dedicated Media has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although we use reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating our security measures does exist.

If you have any questions about our security practices, please send an email to us at [privacy@dedicatedmedia.com](mailto:privacy@dedicatedmedia.com).

**Applicable Laws  
**The Site is operated by Dedicated Media incorporated from its offices in the United States of America. Dedicated Media makes no representation that the information located on the Site is appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to the Site from territories where the content of the Site may be illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access the Site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are

**ADDITIONAL NOTICES AND DISCLOSURES**

**Correspondence  
**If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your email address solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiry. This information will never be shared with third parties.

**Children’s Privacy  
**Dedicated Media is very sensitive to the issue of children’s privacy. Dedicated Media’ websites, products, and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If you believe your child has provided Dedicated Network with personally identifiable data, or registered at one of Dedicated Media’ websites, and you would like to have the data removed, please contact us at [privacy@dedicatedmedia.com](mailto:privacy@dedicatedmedia.com).

**Sale of Assets  
**In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets related to the business, we reserve the right to include any or all stored personal information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.

**Changes to Privacy Policy  
**The issue of privacy is an evolving one. Dedicated Media is committed to the consistent monitoring and examination of its privacy practices and may, from time to time, institute changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any changes are made to the company’s privacy practices, we will post a clear and conspicuous notice of these changes on the Website and in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last revised on January 9, 2012.

**Questions and Comments  
**Questions and comments about your privacy policy should be directed to [privacy@dedicatedmedia.com](mailto:privacy@dedicatedmedia.com) or mailed to:

Privacy  
Dedicated Media, Inc  
909 Sepulveda Blvd, Suite 320  
El Segundo, CA 90245
